The Refuge is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Keith Sutliff.
A getaway driver finds himself in harm's way when he gets caught up in a job
involving casino heist money leading to a debt over his head.
Markus Hunter, played by Keith Sutliff.
Frank, played by Julien Cesario.
Watts Riley, played by Matthew Webb.
Dixon Jones, played by Cheyenne Buchanan.
Virgil, played by Tom Conlan.
Zander, played by Martin Copping.
Safety is a live action short film directed by Fabrice Joubert and produced by Easter Moon Films & Composite Films,
based on the short story Safety written by Lydia Fitzpatrick, about a school shooting in America.
Engaged against gun violence the film has been presented and won
awards in a number of festivals including at L.A.
Film Awards, Lift-Off Los Angeles, Peak City Film
Festival and Miami Short Film Festival.
The tone is emotional and intense.